clickthecity.com 2019-06-15

# ClickTheCity Privacy Policy

At ClickTheCity, we are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When we ask you to provide your personal information when using ClickTheCity Platform, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use, disclosure, and sharing of your personal information when using the ClickTheCity Platform. This Privacy Policy applies to activities by Surf Shop, Inc. (“ClickTheCity”) and its affiliates and subsidiaries.

This Privacy Policy is effective from August 1, 2018.

**What Information We Collect**

When you create your account in ClickTheCity Platform, we shall collect the following personal information. You may decline to submit your personal information to us, but we may not be able to provide certain services to you.

  * Complete Name, Age, and Gender
  * Contact number and Email Address
  * Geographical Location (Latitude and Longitude)
  * Demographic information such as preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**How We Use and Share Your Information**

We assure you that we shall not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. ClickTheCity uses the information to understand your needs and to provide you with a better service and in particular for the following purposes:

  * Internal record keeping.  
 
  * Mobile Ordering Service  
If you use our Mobile Ordering Service, we will transmit your information (name, address, phone number), together with your order to our delivery partners so they can fulfill your order request. Our delivery partners may retain and use your information to send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which you may find interesting.  
 
  * Ticketing Service  
If you use our Ticketing Service, we will transmit your information (name, email address), together with the order information to our cinema partners so they can properly process your ticket purchase. Our cinema partners may retain and use your information to send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which you may find interesting.  
 
  * Privileges / Rewards  
If you use our Privileges / Rewards service, we will transmit your information (name, email address) to our merchant partners so they can provide their respective discounts, offers and promos to you. Our merchant partners may retain and use your information to send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which you may find interesting.  
 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided, but you can opt out at any time.  
 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

**How We Secure and Protect Your Information**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. But we also recommend that you keep your personal information safe by choosing a strong password and keeping it private, and signing-out your user account when you finished using the ClickTheCity Platform, especially when using shared devices.

**How to Access and Update Your Account**

You may update or modify your account information at any time by signing-in to your account on the ClickTheCity Platform.

**Controlling Your Personal Information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Most of our services require that you register with us your personal information. If you don’t want to give us any information: whenever you are asked to fill in a form, just don’t proceed and cancel it.  
 
  * If you believe that any personal information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us at helpdesk@clickthecity.com, and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.  
 
  * If you received a promotional email from us, you can simply click the link that says "Unsubscribe" and we will remove you from our promotional mailing list. Unsubscribing just removes you from our promotional mailing list, but you can still continue to use the account-based services we offer.

**Deleted Accounts**

You may request to delete your account by sending an email to helpdesk@clickthecity.com, with the subject “Delete My Account – [Your email address]” and all your account information will be removed from our database, and by deleting your account you would not be able to access ClickTheCity services that require a user account. However, if you made any transactions on any ClickTheCity services, your transaction logs will remain on the ClickTheCity Platform.

**How We Use Cookies**

ClickTheCity Platform uses industry standard analytics which gathers limited information on visitors automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, the operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as to help us analyze data and improve the website in order to tailor fit it to customer needs.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to ClickTheCity features such as logins and/or repeat visits. A cookie is a small file placed on your computer's hard drive. The file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. But this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the ClickTheCity Platform.

**Third-Party Advertising Networks**

We use third-party advertising networks to serve ads when you visit ClickTheCity Platform. These networks may use information (not including your name, address, email address or contact number) about your visits to ClickTheCity and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

We also use third-party cookies to store and collect information when you visit ClickTheCity for tracking purposes. The companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or contact number) about your visits to ClickTheCity. We only use this data to optimize the performance and experience that you’ll have on ClickTheCity Platform.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Contact Us**

If you have any question or clarification regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@clickthecity.com

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

ClickTheCity may change this privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. You may check this page anytime to ensure that you are updated with any changes on our Privacy Policy. If the changes will affect how we treat your Personal Information, we shall provide you with notice of such changes via a notice in the ClickTheCity platforms or to your registered email address, so we may get your consent or give you the opportunity to opt-out if you do not agree with our updated Privacy Policy.  

Older Versions 

  * August 1, 2017
